striata.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Striata

This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it and how we keep it secure.

We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.

Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent for the attention of the Data Protection Officer, by email to **privacy@striata.com** or by writing to 48 Wall Street, Suite 1100, New York NY, 10005, USA.

## Who are we?

Striata provides strategy, software and professional services that enable digital communication across multiple channels and devices. We are experts in message design, generation, security, delivery and storage. Clients use our technology and services to encrypt, send and store confidential documents; execute integrated marketing campaigns and distribute high volume electronic communications.

## How do we collect information about you?

We obtain information about you under the following circumstances:

  * When you submit the “Contact Us” form;
  * If you subscribe to receive marketing communications such as newsletters and blog notifications;
  * If you request an industry specific demo;
  * When you open or click on an email communication we have sent to you;
  * If you download a document (brochure, whitepaper, case study, etc);
  * If you respond to a job opportunity advertised on our careers page; and/or
  * If you accept our use of cookies to give you a more personal experience.

## What type of information is collected from you?

### For job applications

The personal information we collect is limited to your name, email address, telephone number, Twitter handle, Linkedin page and IP address, plus the date, time and method in which you provided explicit consent to be contacted by an HR representative.

### For Cookies

The personal information we collect is limited to your IP address.

### For all other circumstances

The personal information we collect is limited to your name, email address, region, company, telephone number, industry and IP address, plus the date, time and method in which you provided explicit consent to receive communications from Striata or be contacted by a representative.

If you open or click on a communication we have sent you, we may record that the email was opened on your IP address and what tracked links you click on.

## WHERE WILL YOUR INFORMATION RESIDE?

The personal information we collect will be processed on secure web servers in the following locations:

  * Web: Amazon Web Services, N. Virginia Data center, USA
  * CRM: Amazon Web Services, N. Virginia Data center, USA

 **BY SUBMITTING YOUR INFORMATION, YOU GIVE CONSENT FOR YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO BE SECURELY STORED AND PROCESSED IN THE LOCATIONS STATED ABOVE.**

Should we change the location of our servers, we will notify subscribers and request your consent to process and store your data in the new location.

## How is your information used?

We will only use your information for the purposes stated below:

  * To send marketing communications to you by email (if you have opted in to receive them)
  * To process a job application (if you have submitted one)
  * To contact you about our solutions and services (if you have given consent to be contacted)

## Who has access to your information?

We will not sell, rent or in any way provide your information to a third party for any purpose unless we have your express permission.

We may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of a sale of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganisation. We will share your personal information if we’re under a duty to disclose in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of our employees or customers. However, under any circumstances, we will take all reasonable steps to procure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

## Your choice

You are in control about whether or not you wish to receive marketing information from us. You can manage your choices by selecting the relevant ‘opt-in’ or consent checkbox situated on the form you use to submit your information to us.

 **IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO BE CONTACTED BY US, SIMPLY UN-CHECK THE CONSENT CHECKBOX AND UNSUBSCRIBE FROM ALL STRIATA COMMUNICATIONS.**

We will not contact you for marketing purposes by email, phone or text message unless you have given your prior consent. If you have subscribed and then change your mind, you can change your preferences at any time or you can click on “Unsubscribe” from any newsletter or blog notification. By clicking through to your preferences from these email communications that you have subscribed to, you can unsubscribe by checking the unsubscribe checkbox or un-check the email communication preferences.

## How you can access and update your information

The accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change your email address, or any of the other information we hold becomes inaccurate or out of date, please update your details by clicking through to your preferences on the email footer of any Striata communication.

You have the right to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you. Please complete the Data Subject Request form here. We may complete an authentication process to verify your identity before sharing your information.

EU citizens are given the right (in the GDPR) to request that a company transfer the personal information it holds to another company. Should you require us to transfer your data to another company, please complete the Data Subject Request form here. Once the transfer has been completed, we will delete your personal information unless we are required to maintain records for compliance with the law.

If you wish to exercise your right to be forgotten (i.e. have all your information deleted from our system), you may request this by completing the Data Subject Request form here. We will remove your personal information from our systems, except where the deletion: (i) is prohibited by law; or (ii) involves residual or back-up data that is not technically feasible to return to Client, provided that the Striata will destroy or delete such residual or back-up data in accordance with its standard backup retention policies.

## Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information

When you give us your personal information, we take steps to ensure that it is processed and stored securely.

If you submit information to us from a form on our website, that information is protected using a secure method (HTTPS). We cannot vouch for the security of information you transmit to us VIA OTHER MEANS, and you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

## Profiling

We may analyse information about you to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can provide information relevant to you.

## Use of ‘cookies’

In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the [About Cookies website](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers.

Our website uses ‘cookies’ – these are small pieces of information sent by an organisation, website or web application to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow our website to recognise your session when you visit. We collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. For example, we use cookies to 1) track an estimate of the country that you are in (note that content is NOT altered/hidden based on your location), 2) Show/hide status of the cookie notice bar and 3) allow for Google Analytics and Clicky tracking status on your visit session . This helps us to improve our website and deliver a better more personalised service, yet still ensuring that no personal information is accessible in the cookies.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites (and cookies) run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website.

In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.

## Minors

In order to protect the privacy of children who are considered minors, only individuals who are 18 and older are permitted to provide personal information via our website. We will not knowingly process or store information about minors, and any minors that do submit information to us, agree that they have the permission of a parent or guardian.

## EU Citizens

### Transferring your information outside of Europe

As part of the services offered to you through this website, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (“EU”). By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of the EU. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the UK. By submitting your personal data, you’re agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing. If we transfer your information outside of the EU in this way, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Policy.

### Submitting a Data Request

Please use our Data Subject Request form found here to exercise any of your rights as a data subject.

## Website recording

We use Google Analytics and Clicky to track click events, page views and goal conversions like submitting a contact us or career application form on the website. The information collected is used to improve our website usability and is stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting. This information cannot be used to identify you.

## Review of this Policy

We keep this Policy under regular review. This Policy was last updated in **25 May 2018**.

You can link through to this latest version of the Policy from the email footer of the most recent communication you receive from us.
